(Sheldon:)with strange men leaving
her apartment in the morning,
(Sheldon:)plus the number of times
(Sheldon:)she's returned home
wearing the same clothes
(Sheldon:)she wore the night before...
(Penny:)Okay, Sheldon, I think
you've made your point.
(Sheldon:)So we multiply 193--
(Sheldon:)minus 21 men
before the loss of virginity--
(Sheldon:)so 172
(Sheldon:)times 0.18 gives us...
(Sheldon:)30.96 sexual partners.
(Sheldon:)Let's round that up to 31.
(Penny:)Okay, Sheldon, you are so wrong.
(Penny:)That is not even close
to the real number.
(Penny:)I'm gonna need
a drink over here.
(Amy:)This is very interesting.
(Amy:)Cultural perceptions
are subjective.
(Amy:)Penny, to your mind,
are you a slut?
(Penny:)No! No!
(Howard:)No.
(Penny:)Let's just all finish
our dinners, okay?
(Sheldon:)This is
an interesting topic.
(Sheldon:)How many sexual encounters
have you had?
(Amy:)Does volunteering
for a scientific experiment
(Amy:)in which orgasm was achieved
by electronically
stimulating the pleasure centers
of the brain count?